y O
most O
anxious O
and O
seriou O
knew O
to O
ththis O
arguments O
but O
So O
regret O
thmy O
inabilty O
go O
sustaining O
it. O

The O
acquisition O
procedings O
been O
has O
challeged O
on O
thehe O
groud O
that O
notification O
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
6 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
Land B-STATUTE
Acquisition I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
is O
before O
expiration O
ofd O
one O
month O
of O
thehe O
notification O
published O
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
4 I-PROVISION
. O

counsel O
that O
imporant O
factual O
either O
circumstances O
were O
purposefully O
supressed O
fromn O
thehe O
Holding O
Company O
either O
that O
thehe O
lettter O
of O
offers O
andnd O
thehe O
notices O
of O
the O
Board's O
meeting O
ofd O
April O
2 O
werer O
deliberately O
posted O
early O
on O
December O
27. O

expandir O
30 O
of O
thehe O
judgement O
in O
the O
case O
of O
Sabita B-OTHER_PERSON
Prasad I-OTHER_PERSON
It O
misquoted O
thereunder O
- O

Let O
us O
assuming O
fofor O
an O
minutes O
an O
hypothetic O
situation O
whre O
thehe O
Trial O
Courts O
waited O
granting O
an O
ad O
interim O
ex O
parte O
injuction O
andnd O
the O
defendant O
in O
thehe O
suit O
file O
one O
appliction O
fofor O
vacating O
thehe O
interim O
injunction O
andnd O
another O
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
45 I-PROVISION
. O

Its O
lands O
ofd O
his O
paternal O
aunts O
Nathuram B-OTHER_PERSON
andnd O
Prem B-OTHER_PERSON
is O
really O
adjacent O
to O
the O
field O
ofd O
thehe O
informants O
and O
him O
father O
Hariram B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

At O
thehe O
smae O
month O
1978 O
him O
encroached O
apon O
acres O
of O
dhu O
mazrua O
land O
belonging O
to O
thehe O
State B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bihar I-ORG
in O
villages O
Bagra B-GPE
in O
thehe O
district O
ofd O
Gopalganj B-GPE
, O

The O
administraton O
of O
sorts O
those O
United O
was O
handing O
around O
to O
the O
Raj-pramukh B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

The O
not O
laws O
which O
It O
cited O
in O
suppport O
ofd O
thehe O
accusing O
It O
Section B-PROVISION
7 I-PROVISION
and O
the O
Schedules O
of O
thehe O
extradited O
offence O
appeared O
in O
the O
Indian B-STATUTE
Extradition I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
1903 I-STATUTE
. O
16. O

he O
market O
well O
Simla O
cigarette O
ofd O
thehe O
appellant O

All O
cases O
fromn O
thehe O
specifed O
Oudh B-GPE
area O
are O
meant O
to O
is O
heard O
amAt O
Lucknow B-GPE
. O

Its O
petitioner O
claims O
23 O
decade O
ofd O
stading O
in O
operating O
stage O
carriage O
andnd O
alos O
experience O
along O
an O
minor O
portion O
ofd O
the O
two O
route O
in O
quesion O
that O
are O
three O
looong O
faraway O
routes O
in O
the O
Palghat B-GPE
district I-GPE
. O

There O
should O
be O
cases O
where O
even O
an O
delays O
ofd O
a O
lengthier O
period O
may O
is O
regarded O
go O
is O
insufficient O
go O
refuse O
releif O
in O
a O
petition O
underthe O
Article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

The O
arguably O
imporant O
witness O
It O
certainly O
Keshar B-WITNESS
Singh I-WITNESS
. O

Before O
we O
come O
to O
thehe O
contention O
ofd O
Mr. O
Narendra B-OTHER_PERSON
Mohan I-OTHER_PERSON
Kasliwal I-OTHER_PERSON
in O
repsect O
ofd O
rasing O
ofd O
upper O
age O
limits O
for O
admission O
go O
Hospital O
Universities O
fromn O
21 O
years O
to O
22 O
years O
I O
consider O
so O
proper O
to O
deal O
with O
thehe O
othe O
two O
categories O
ofd O
resevations O
that O
been O
has O
challeged O
byh O
Mr. O
Mridul B-OTHER_PERSON
in O
additon O
go O
these O
assaulted O
by O
Mr. O
Narendra B-OTHER_PERSON
Mohan I-OTHER_PERSON
Kasliwal I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

At O
those O
circumstance O
thehe O
Court O
observed O
that O
intrest O
It O
available O
on O
anything O
amount O
of O
refun O
ththat O
It O
given O
to O
thehe O
assessee O
Under O
Section B-PROVISION
240 I-PROVISION
. O
24. O

At O
the O
smae O
time O
Mahendra B-OTHER_PERSON
Pal I-OTHER_PERSON
went O
out O
of O
thehe O
Kothari O
from O
thehe O
south-east O
sides O
and O
him O
wasn O
also O
shots O
amAt O
and O
him O
falling O
down O
in O
thehe O
drains O
and O
wasn O
assualted O
byh O
Banka B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

The O
aforesaid O
Clause B-PROVISION
VIII I-PROVISION
postulates O
the O
ESTATERETAILCONSUMERPHONESCARSBIKESAPPSINTERNETTABLETSCOMPUTERSSOCIETYPOLITICSLAWCRIMEENVIRONMENTSCIENCEARTSCELEBRITIESSPORTSSPECIALSFIRST O
of O
addtional O
taxes O
amAt O
thehe O
lowest O
approriate O
rates O
on O
as O
vehicles O
which O
becoming O
nontaxable O
under O
more O
less O
only O
ofd O
the O
article O
ofd O
Schedule B-PROVISION
IV I-PROVISION
. O

ion O
to O
proceed O
underthe O
thehe O
Act O

Related O
notices O
were O
issued O
go O
othe O
co-sharers O
in O
the O
Noori B-ORG
Sugar I-ORG
Works I-ORG
. O

Similar O
wasn O
thehe O
postion O
in O
thehe O
other O
case O
ofd O
Commissioner B-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
Income-tax I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Hukumchand I-PRECEDENT
Mohanlal I-PRECEDENT
. O

her O
was O
treat O
amAt O
Allahabad B-GPE
and O
Lucknow B-GPE
. O

Nachhatar B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
sons O
of O
Sadhu B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
residents O
ofd O
Jalandhar O
Road O
NagarMehsanaVadodaraAnandBhavnagarKachchhSabarkanthaJunagadhJamnagarGurgaonRohtakFaridabadSonepatHisarAmbalaYamuna O
District B-GPE
Sangrur I-GPE
. O
... O
Appellant O
Versus O
1- O
Mukhtiar B-OTHER_PERSON
Kaur I-OTHER_PERSON
husband O
of O
Surjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
son O
ofd O
Harnam B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
2- O
Surjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
sons O
of O
Harnam B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
andnd O
3- O
Karnail B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
son O
ofd O
Surjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
residents O
of O
village O
Golewala B-GPE
. O

He O
spoke O
him O
son O
Bhausaheb B-OTHER_PERSON
to O
taking O
him O
motor O
cycle O
go O
punctures O
repairs O
shops O
of O
Badrimama B-GPE
. O

No O
modifcation O
will O
be O
made O
byh O
the O
courts O
in O
exercise O
ofd O
powers O
underthe O
Article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
of O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
India I-STATUTE
. O

her O
followed O
herself O
and O
reboarded O
a O
trains O
andnd O
reached O
a O
place O
before O
crossed O
an O
bridges O
fromn O
whre O
her O
took O
thehe O
Digha O
bound O
buses O
and O
reached O
amAt O
Contai B-GPE
. O
INVESTIGATIONS O
9. O

He O
watched O
fofor O
an O
whilst O
but O
he O
could O
necessarily O
finding O
Munni B-OTHER_PERSON
Bai I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

For O
reasons O
that O
we O
been O
already O
given O
I O
respecfully O
dissents O
fromn O
thehe O
view O
I O
took O
byh O
the O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

Insurance O
Company O
objecting O
go O
thehe O
maintainable O
of O
thehe O
claim O
petitions O
andnd O
loci O
standi O
of O
thehe O
claimant O
to O
file O
it. O

On O
arrrival O
in O
India B-GPE
, O
ththey O
registere O
themselves O
as O
refugee O
andnd O
complied O
with O
few O
othe O
formality O
required O
of O
an O
refugees O
from O
Sri B-GPE
Lanka I-GPE
. O

Its O
accident O
is O
said O
go O
been O
occurred O
on O
Bombay B-GPE
- O
Pune B-GPE
Highwa O
nearby O
Nalgaon B-GPE
Village I-GPE
, O
withing O
the O
territory O
jurisdication O
of O
Wadagaon-Moval B-ORG
Police I-ORG
Station I-ORG
. O

He O
alos O
particpated O
in O
thehe O
chases O
and O
in O
thehe O
arrest O
of O
7 O
person O
at O
village O
Chandrahatti B-GPE
, O
whom O
waited O
injuries O
andnd O
alos O
came O
to O
Hajipur B-GPE
andnd O
saw O
ththat O
15 O
persons O
had O
been O
arrested O
there O
including O
Appellees O
Anand B-PETITIONER
Mohan I-PETITIONER
and O
Lovely B-PETITIONER
Anand I-PETITIONER
. O

Its O
Petitioners O
belonging O
or O
go O
the O
Madhya B-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
District I-ORG
Police I-ORG
Force I-ORG
or O
the O
Madhya B-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
special I-ORG
Armed I-ORG
Force I-ORG
. O

Dr. O
N. B-OTHER_PERSON
M. I-OTHER_PERSON
Ghatate I-OTHER_PERSON
for O
Petitioner O
in O
CA. B-CASE_NUMBER
1658/80 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

naire O
aspect O
ofd O
it. O

The O
second O
cases O
is O
the O
decison O
ofd O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
in O
Bimal B-PRECEDENT
Chandra I-PRECEDENT
Banerjee I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
State I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
Madhya I-PRECEDENT
Pradesh I-PRECEDENT
AIR I-PRECEDENT
1959 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
169 I-PRECEDENT
. O

Sureshwar B-OTHER_PERSON
Jha I-OTHER_PERSON
was O
treated O
in O
Rahman B-OTHER_PERSON
's O
Nursin O
Home O
and O
from O
theres O
he O
wasn O
refers O
go O
Patna B-GPE
. O

It O
It O
ththis O
conflicts O
ththat O
is O
reflecting O
in O
these O
cases O
refers O
to O
the O
Constitution B-COURT
Bench I-COURT
. O

He O
wasn O
follwed O
by O
Mr. O
Som B-OTHER_PERSON
Nath I-OTHER_PERSON
Iyer I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
learned O
counsel O
for O
thehe O
petitioner O
Union O
in O
Civil B-CASE_NUMBER
Appeal I-CASE_NUMBER
2317 I-CASE_NUMBER
of I-CASE_NUMBER
1972 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

Earlier O
their O
names O
was O
Chowdhry B-ORG
Plast I-ORG
Ltd. I-ORG

So O
been O
waited O
the O
benefit O
ofd O
reading O
in O
adavance O
the O
judgement O
of O
my O
learnt O
Brothe O
Chinnappa B-JUDGE
Reddy I-JUDGE
, O
J. O

Second O
provisos O
to O
section B-PROVISION
143 I-PROVISION
ofd O
the O
Act O
ofd O
1881 O
carve O
out O
two O
exeptions O
to O
trying O
a O
complaints O
by O
summons O
trials O
case O
either O
othe O
procedure O
given O
underthe O
CrPC B-STATUTE
. O

Its O
wife O
was O
employed O
in O
Delhi B-GPE
andnd O
him O
would O
necessarily O
is O
expect O
go O
leaving O
his O
job O
and O
try O
to O
winning O
bakc O
the O
affection O
andnd O
confidence O
of O
his O
husband O
in O
herself O
parent's O
house O
amAt O
Aligarh B-GPE
. O

He O
payed O
thehe O
requisites O
tax O
till O
the O
quarters O
ending O
31st B-DATE
March I-DATE
1974 I-DATE
. O

These O
appeal O
by O
ecial O
leave O
are O
directed O
againt O
an O
Orders O
passed O
byh O
thehe O
Divison O
Bench O
of O
the O
Karnataka B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
unceremoniously O
reject O
writs O
appeal O
perferred O
byh O
several O
students O
against O
an O
common O
judgement O
deliver O
by O
Justic O
Rama B-JUDGE
Jois I-JUDGE
dismiss O
the O
writ O
petition O
refiled O
by O
themselves O
challenge O
thehe O
cancellation O
ofd O
their O
admissions O
byh O
the O
Karnataka B-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

Another O
of O
themselves O
wasn O
Simranjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
Mann I-OTHER_PERSON
who O
had O
has O
dimissed O
fromn O
the O
Indian B-ORG
Police I-ORG
Service I-ORG
. O

But O
the O
princples O
ofd O
Engish O
law O
cannnot O
determine O
thehe O
jurisdiction O
ofd O
thehe O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
, O
for O
so O
will O
amuse O
an O
petitions O
underthe O
Article B-PROVISION
32 I-PROVISION
only O
fofor O
thehe O
enforcement O
of O
righs O
conferring O
in O
Part B-PROVISION
III I-PROVISION
of O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

K. B-OTHER_PERSON
B. I-OTHER_PERSON
Asthana I-OTHER_PERSON
fofor O
the O
State B-GPE
of I-GPE
Uttar I-GPE
Pradesh I-GPE
. O

Special O
Commisioner O
cum O
Transportation O
Commisioner O
Chepauk B-GPE
Chennai-600 I-GPE
005 O
3. O

Article B-PROVISION
246 I-PROVISION
andnd O
List O
I O
conferring O
certain O
specfic O
powers O
on O
Parliament B-ORG
. O

is O
It O
baed O
on O
thehe O
use O
of O
thehe O
word O
no O
as O
files O
is O
in O
existences O
that O
making O
thehe O
appellant O
contending O
before O
the O
High O
Court O
that O
an O
deliberate O
correct O
statement O
wasn O
making O
byh O
the O
CBI B-ORG
in O
its O
affidavits O
filed O
before O
thehe O
Low O
Courts O
wtih O
an O
view O
go O
deny O
thehe O
allegation O
making O
byh O
the O
writ O
petitioners O

We O
are O
clearly O
unbound O
go O
follow O
thehe O
said O
judgment O
ofd O
thehe O
Constitution B-COURT
Bench I-COURT
. O

He O
has O
furhter O
contends O
ththat O
the O
Sate O
Governement O
approached O
thehe O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
before O
take O
decison O
to O
abolish O
the O
Tribunal O
fofor O
issuance O
ofd O
the O
requisites O
notifcation O
but O
so O
was O
of O
the O
impressions O
ththat O
the O
notifcation O
would O
is O
issuing O
byh O
the O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
. O

Its O
smae O
applies O
good O
though O
go O
appellant O
Jagpal B-PETITIONER
. O

Mr. O
Joshi B-OTHER_PERSON
relied O
upon O
thehe O
decison O
ofd O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
in O
Commissioner B-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
Income-tax I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Kumbakonam I-PRECEDENT
Mutual I-PRECEDENT
Benefit I-PRECEDENT
Fund I-PRECEDENT
Ltd. I-PRECEDENT

Its O
learned O
Counsels O
fofor O
thehe O
respondent O
resubmitted O
ththat O
I O
should O
perfer O
thehe O
view O
expressing O
by O
Shivashankar B-JUDGE
Bhat I-JUDGE
, O
J. O
in O
the O
case O
ofd O
Balappa B-OTHER_PERSON
in O
preferences O
to O
the O
view O
expressed O
byh O
Swami B-JUDGE
, O
J. O
that O
was O
affirmed O
in O
thehe O
cases O
of O
Gwalior B-OTHER_PERSON
Rayon I-OTHER_PERSON
andnd O
thehe O
Divison O
Bench O
in O
the O
case O
ofd O
Lakshmi B-OTHER_PERSON
Bai I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

her O
could O
be O
taugh O
by O
thehe O
stepfather O
ofd O
thehe O
appellant O
whom O
wasn O
working O
as O
Lecturer O
Professor O
in O
City B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chicago I-ORG
. O

There O
are O
Bench O
ofd O
those O
Tribunals O
in O
thehe O
State B-ORG
of I-ORG
Madhya I-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
but O
itheir O
major O
seats O
aren O
ouside O
the O
State B-ORG
of I-ORG
Madhya I-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
. O

Its O
findings O
are O
necessarily O
apposed O
go O
justic O
either O
morality O
or O
contrary O
to O
the O
publc O
policies O
ofd O
India B-GPE
. O

Both O
thehe O
Tehsils O
fall O
in O
district O
Ghaziabad B-GPE
. O

The O
investigating O
officers O
alongwith O
the O
cops O
officials O
once O
again O
once O
visted O
thehe O
prepaid O
taxis O
parking O
lot O
amAt O
the O
IGI B-ORG
Airport I-ORG
. O

Its O
wife O
is O
an O
Advocate O
practiced O
in O
this O
Courts O
as O
as O
well O
in O
Delhi B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

Its O
petitioner's O
stepfather O
orginally O
lived O
at O
Umreth B-GPE
, O
whilst O
the O
original O
palce O
of O
residence O
ofd O
thehe O
respondent O
It O
Vaso B-GPE
. O

The O
learnt O
Counsels O
fofor O
thehe O
parties O
informed O
that O
the O
mattter O
is O
stilll O
necessarily O
opted O
byh O
the O
smaller O
Bench O
ofd O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

That O
wasn O
thehe O
decision O
ofd O
Santosh B-JUDGE
, O
J. O
go O
that O
So O
have O
referred O
to O
earlier O
in O
thehe O
cases O
of O
Laxmimanojana B-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Sujnandra I-PRECEDENT
. O

Onkar B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
Lakhawat I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
learnt O
counsels O
furhter O
argues O
that O
merely O
failures O
ofd O
appellant O
Sohani B-PETITIONER
to O
preventing O
thehe O
offence O
cannot O
be O
took O
well O
proofs O
go O
holding O
her O
guilty O
for O
offences O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
302 I-PROVISION
of O
thehe O
IPC B-STATUTE
. O

He O
recorded O
the O
statments O
of O
complainants O
Ashok B-OTHER_PERSON
Kumar I-OTHER_PERSON
Jain I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
abductees O
Vikash B-OTHER_PERSON
Jain I-OTHER_PERSON
and O
witnesses O
Prakash B-WITNESS
Singh I-WITNESS
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
161 I-PROVISION
ofd O
CrPC B-STATUTE
. O

Its O
punishments O
wasn O
enhanced O
and O
thehe O
offences O
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
354 I-PROVISION
IPC B-STATUTE
It O
made O
a O
non-bailable O
only O
in O
thehe O
State O
of O
Andhra B-GPE
Pradesh I-GPE
. O

The O
othe O
article O
in O
the O
second O
divison O
to O
thehe O
schedules O
referred O
to O
applcations O
underthe O
thehe O
Arbitration B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
andnd O
also O
in O
two O
cases O
exeption O
ofd O
applcations O
underthe O
the O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Criminal I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
. O

Let O
me O
now O
turning O
to O
the O
evidences O
ofd O
P. O
W. O
5 O
Somnath B-WITNESS
Sen. I-WITNESS

THE O
MANAGERS O
KVC B-ORG
BANK I-ORG
MUGAD I-ORG
BRANCH I-ORG
TQ I-ORG
& I-ORG
DIST I-ORG
: I-ORG
DHARWAD I-ORG
28. O

Another O
spokesman O
of O
thehe O
Buddhists O
community O
who O
deposed O
Defacement O
thehe O
Commisison O
wasn O
Shri O
R. B-OTHER_PERSON
S. I-OTHER_PERSON
Gavai I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
Chairman O
of O
thehe O
Maharashtra B-ORG
State I-ORG
Legislative I-ORG
Council I-ORG
. O

After O
completion O
ofd O
investigation O
him O
been O
submitted O
thehe O
charges O
sheet O
against O
the O
accused O
for O
thehe O
offence O
jailable O
underthe O
Sections B-PROVISION
376 I-PROVISION
and I-PROVISION
420 I-PROVISION
ofd O
IPC B-STATUTE
. O
5. O

It O
wasn O
foudn O
at O
thehe O
tiem O
ofd O
thehe O
arguments O
after O
the O
Sales B-COURT
Tax I-COURT
Tribunal I-COURT
that O
soem O
ofd O
the O
entries O
which O
werer O
foudn O
in O
the O
jote O
of O
Jayantilal B-ORG
Thakordas I-ORG
& I-ORG
Co. I-ORG
, O
well O
mantained O
byh O
thehe O
Angadia B-OTHER_PERSON
, O
had O
corresponds O
debit O
entries O
in O
thehe O
accounts O
books O
of O
the O
assessee-firm O
well O
havig O
has O
paid O
byh O
thehe O
assessee-firm O
go O
thehe O
Angadia B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

The O
action O
of O
the O
Income-tax O
authorites O
wasn O
affirmed O
byh O
an O
Pull O
Bench O
of O
thehe O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

Her O
Lordship O
of O
thehe O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
have O
alos O
reapproved O
thehe O
above O
princples O
in O
itheir O
decision O
reported O
in O
AIR B-PRECEDENT
1957 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
912 I-PRECEDENT
. O
66. O

The O
accused O
werer O
simultaneoulsy O
atacking O
PW2 O
and O
Baiju B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

Thus O
this O
courts O
go O
necessarily O
finding O
anything O
force O
in O
the O
argument O
advanced O
byh O
thehe O
learnt O
counsel O
fofor O
thehe O
complainant O
that O
the O
accused O
has O
failing O
go O
refute O
the O
assumption O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
139 I-PROVISION
of O
thehe O
NI B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

That O
collisions O
took O
place O
abour O
eight O
kilometers O
from O
Bhatia B-GPE
toward O
Dwarka B-GPE
betweeen O
1.30 O
and O
1.45 O
P. O
M. O

Decease O
Manjunath B-OTHER_PERSON
Ithal I-OTHER_PERSON
wasn O
having O
Sweet O
Wal O
at O
Shimoga B-GPE
. O

In O
an O
statements O
refiled O
on O
behalfs O
ofd O
the O
petitioner O
so O
is O
noted O
ththat O
in O
repsect O
of O
thehe O
purchase O
made O
in O
Calcutta B-GPE
the O
document O
of O
titles O
were O
receieved O
by O
post O
in O
Madras B-GPE
. O

Its O
deceased O
was O
taken O
in O
the O
autorickshaws O
go O
othe O
places O
andnd O
finally O
returning O
go O
Kuthirakadavu B-GPE
. O

Its O
Insurance O
Company O
has O
failing O
go O
explaining O
think O
ththey O
have O
took O
extra O
premuim O
ofd O
three O
passengers O
when O
thehe O
statutorily O
requirement O
ofd O
policy O
wasn O
already O
covered O
Under O
Section B-PROVISION
147 I-PROVISION
ofd O
Motor B-STATUTE
Vehicle I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

The O
Courts O
notice O
that O
Section B-PROVISION
163­A I-PROVISION
wasn O
inserted O
making O
a O
deviations O
fromn O
thehe O
common O
laws O
liablity O
underthe O
the O
Law O
ofd O
CivPro O
andnd O
alos O
in O
derogation O
of O
the O
provision O
ofd O
thehe O
Fatal B-STATUTE
Accidents I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

At O
Kameswar B-PRECEDENT
Prosad I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
State I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
Bihar I-PRECEDENT
and O
O. B-PRECEDENT
K. I-PRECEDENT
Ghose I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Ex I-PRECEDENT
Joseph I-PRECEDENT
it O
been O
been O
held O
ththat O
thehe O
righ O
go O
strikes O
is O
not O
an O
fundamental O
righ O
guarantee O
by O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

Its O
above O
decison O
wasn O
subsequentially O
followed O
by O
thehe O
smae O
Bench O
in O
Reckitt B-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Colman I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
India I-PRECEDENT
Ltd. I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
CIT I-PRECEDENT
. O

Thereafter O
the O
Superintendent O
andnd O
the O
partys O
made O
a O
through O
seach O
in O
thehe O
presences O
of O
thehe O
independant O
eyewitnesses O
, O
thehe O
occupants O
andnd O
thehe O
accountants O
ofd O
thehe O
hotel O
, O
Mr. O
Jayaprakash B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

A O
noncompensatory O
taxes O
is O
ouside O
thehe O
purview O
of O
article B-PROVISION
301 I-PROVISION
as O
thehe O
taxes O
It O
intended O
to O
creating O
facilites O
fofor O
trades O
and O
promoting O
thehe O
free-flow O
ofd O
trade O
andnd O
not O
to O
impede O
it. O

So O
alos O
directing O
a O
copies O
ofd O
that O
Rule O
go O
is O
served O
on O
thehe O
fifth O
respondent O
Subodh B-RESPONDENT
Chandra I-RESPONDENT
Bose I-RESPONDENT
. O

The O
smae O
would O
been O
influences O
thehe O
learnt O
single O
Judge O
in O
thehe O
said O
case O
to O
express O
thehe O
view O
ththat O
all O
the O
Court O
functioning O
withing O
thehe O
district O
allotted O
to O
thehe O
Permenant O
BenchThe O
amAt O
Madurai B-GPE
aren O
subordinate O
also O
go O
thehe O
Principal O
BenchThe O
at O
Chennai B-GPE
. O

Its O
trials O
Court O
negatived O
the O
contention O
that O
aren O
saught O
go O
be O
rasied O
after O
ththis O
Courts O
also O
andnd O
acquitted O
grassrots O
the O
eight O
accused O
persons O
for O
thehe O
offence O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
302 I-PROVISION
read O
wtih O
Section B-PROVISION
149 I-PROVISION
ofd O
the O
Indian B-STATUTE
Penal I-STATUTE
Code I-STATUTE
. O
5. O

At O
AIR B-PRECEDENT
1954 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
39 I-PRECEDENT
, O
the O
factual O
were O
ththat O
a O
dacoity O
waited O
has O
comitted O
in O
the O
houses O
ofd O
one O
Namdeo B-OTHER_PERSON
Moti I-OTHER_PERSON
Ram I-OTHER_PERSON
in O
the O
night O
ofd O
thehe O
11th B-DATE
of I-DATE
December I-DATE
1950 I-DATE
. O

It O
It O
strange O
well O
go O
what O
the O
petitioner O
would O
claims O
knowledge O
of O
thehe O
recomendations O
ofd O
thehe O
Chief O
Justice O
ofd O
India B-GPE
and O
Chief O
Justic O
ofd O
Delhi B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

is O
also O
appear O
from O
paragraphs O
4.6 O
of O
Chapter O
IV O
ofd O
IPart O
III O
ofd O
thehe O
report O
ofd O
thehe O
Fourth B-ORG
Central I-ORG
Pay I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
ththat O
thehe O
Commisison O
would O
necessarily O
undertake O
an O
detailled O
studies O
of O
thehe O
job O
contents O
andnd O
different O
fuctions O
in O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

The O
plaintiffs O
Kaki B-PETITIONER
andnd O
Har B-PETITIONER
Kaur I-PETITIONER
refiled O
an O
suit O
for O
ajoint O
possession O
ofd O
thehe O
property O
ofd O
deceaseds O
Chanan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

But O
thehe O
employers O
is O
bound O
underthe O
thehe O
Statute O
go O
making O
an O
equals O
contributions O
up O
go O
a O
minimum O
prescribed O
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
6 I-PROVISION
. O

The O
powe O
to O
legislating O
in O
repsect O
of O
treaty O
lie O
with O
thehe O
Parliament B-ORG
underthe O
Entires B-PROVISION
10 I-PROVISION
and I-PROVISION
14 I-PROVISION
of I-PROVISION
List I-PROVISION
I I-PROVISION
of I-PROVISION
the I-PROVISION
Seventh I-PROVISION
Schedule I-PROVISION
. O

Onto O
ththis O
constitutional O
pattern O
ofd O
oneness O
interwoven O
byh O
thehe O
Founding O
Mothers O
wasn O
refitted O
Article B-PROVISION
141 I-PROVISION
which O
gave O
to O
evey O
declarations O
of O
laws O
by O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
a O
binding O
supremecy O
thoughout O
thehe O
territory O
ofd O
India B-GPE
. O

Similarly O
whre O
an O
wife O
misuse O
either O
though O
appropriating O
any O
propety O
exlusively O
belonged O
to O
his O
wife O
withing O
thehe O
matrimony O
home O
him O
hardly O
comes O
within O
the O
ambit O
of O
criminalities O
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
406 I-PROVISION
, O
Indian B-STATUTE
Penal I-STATUTE
Code I-STATUTE
. O

Petitioner O
Pradeep B-RESPONDENT
been O
noted O
that O
he O
was O
in O
servicee O
in O
NOIDA B-ORG
andnd O
was O
residing O
seperately O
from O
thehe O
petitioner O
Kuldeep B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

Appellant O
Raj B-PETITIONER
Pal I-PETITIONER
attempted O
go O
lift O
thehe O
body O
but O
would O
necessarily O
andnd O
then O
Gurbachan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
came O
an O
bamboos O
ladder O
andnd O
with O
the O
helps O
of O
ladders O
ththey O
dump O
the O
dead O
body O
in O
the O
skeptic O
tanks O
located O
on O
thehe O
southern O
sides O
ofd O
thehe O
bungalows O
compounds O
of O
Suresh B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

For O
Gujarat O
view O
see O
Naren B-PRECEDENT
Anappa I-PRECEDENT
Shethi I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Jayantilal I-PRECEDENT
Shah I-PRECEDENT
, O
. O

Sudesh B-OTHER_PERSON
waited O
conceal O
the O
knife O
andnd O
tiffin O
in O
his O
Villlage O
Uhlawas B-GPE
at O
him O
houses O
about O
that O
him O
thought O
and O
none O
elese O
thought O
about O
it. O

Its O
3rd O
accusing O
Kishore B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
meet O
thehe O
2nd O
accused O
Rameshdevji B-OTHER_PERSON
Shah I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
in O
connection O
wtih O
the O
import O
of O
cargoes O
to O
USA B-GPE
. O

was O
reaffirmed O
byh O
this O
Courts O
in O
Bhut B-PRECEDENT
Nath I-PRECEDENT
Mete I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
State I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
West I-PRECEDENT
Bengal I-PRECEDENT
. O

Some O
categories O
of O
teachers O
reappointed O
aleady O
werer O
protecte O
byh O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

The O
land O
aren O
Governement O
Poramboke O
lands O
andnd O
thehe O
Governement O
has O
evey O
righ O
to O
alienate O
the O
same O
go O
Neyveli B-ORG
Lignite I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
. O

So O
per O
that O
inquiry O
it O
wasn O
reveals O
that O
deceaseds O
Jug B-OTHER_PERSON
Lal I-OTHER_PERSON
wasn O
serve O
in O
Armys O
who O
waited O
married O
Sarti B-OTHER_PERSON
Devi I-OTHER_PERSON
though O
in O
1950 O
Sarti B-OTHER_PERSON
Devi I-OTHER_PERSON
expired O
leave O
only O
granddaughter O
Omvati B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

While O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
came O
intot O
effect O
an O
numbers O
of O
case O
have O
has O
vanished O
to O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
wtih O
reference O
go O
Article B-PROVISION
311 I-PROVISION
. O

It O
wasn O
the O
case O
ofd O
the O
appellants O
ththat O
Section B-PROVISION
33 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
VAT B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
willl O
necessarily O
apply O
for O
reopening O
assessments O
pertaining O
go O
Entry B-STATUTE
Tax I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

withing O
a O
few O
months O
either O
though O
an O
couple O
weeks O
before O
it. O

In O
ththis O
cases O
it O
is O
necessarily O
seriously O
dispute O
byh O
thehe O
Sate O
ththat O
the O
plaintiffs O
werer O
citizens O
ofd O
India B-GPE
amAt O
the O
commencements O
of O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

The O
Full O
Bench O
of O
thehe O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
holding O
that O
the O
impugned O
Act O
didn O
necessarily O
trenches O
apon O
thehe O
excusive O
powers O
of O
the O
Federal O
Legislators O
andnd O
thehe O
observations O
quoted O
above O
werer O
making O
in O
uphold O
thehe O
decison O
ofd O
thehe O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

P. O
W. O
1 O
deposed O
in O
his O
evidences O
ththat O
by O
once O
him O
did O
not O
know O
ththat O
him O
names O
wasn O
T. B-OTHER_PERSON
Hanumantha I-OTHER_PERSON
Rao I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

Read O
over O
the O
cheques O
in O
ththat O
case O
was O
one O
draw O
on O
an O
foreign O
banks O
and O
the O
presention O
to O
the O
indorser O
banks O
wasn O
necessarily O
withing O
thehe O
territories O
of O
India B-GPE
. O

That O
postion O
has O
still O
been O
settled O
byh O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

A O
conductor O
was O
asked O
to O
posses O
Conductor's O
licence O
as O
well O
well O
drivng O
licences O
withouth O
amendment O
in O
thehe O
RegulationsThe O
well O
per O
Section B-PROVISION
45 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
State B-STATUTE
Road I-STATUTE
Transport I-STATUTE
Corporation I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

He O
then O
refers O
go O
and O
rely O
on O
thehe O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
cases O
of O
Mahasay B-PRECEDENT
Ganesh I-PRECEDENT
Prasad I-PRECEDENT
Ray I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Narendra I-PRECEDENT
Nath I-PRECEDENT
Sen I-PRECEDENT
AIR I-PRECEDENT
1953 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
431 I-PRECEDENT
in O
suppport O
ofd O
the O
propositions O
ththat O
the O
loose O
papers O
seizing O
would O
not O
be O
considered O
well O
accounts O
within O
thehe O
meanings O
ofd O
Section B-PROVISION
90 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
Evidence B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

is O
It O
writ O
small O
ththat O
the O
issues O
have O
aleady O
has O
finallly O
putting O
to O
rest O
before O
thehe O
orders O
ofd O
thehe O
Hon'ble O
Delhi B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
andnd O
thehe O
dismissals O
of O
the O
SLPs O
by O
the O
Hon'ble O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

It O
It O
also O
observed O
in O
thehe O
same O
judgment O
byh O
Hon'ble O
Low O
Courts O
ththat O
theres O
is O
there O
notifcation O
by O
that O
the O
DRC B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
been O
has O
extended O
go O
thehe O
areas O
of O
Delhi B-GPE
that O
falls O
in O
thehe O
Sub O
Divison O
North O
East O
Delhi B-GPE
, O
Village O
Najafgarh B-GPE
. O

c. O
Its O
charge O
framed O
in O
SC B-CASE_NUMBER
254/2006 I-CASE_NUMBER
andshall O
be O
altered O
in O
inaccordance O
with O
laws O
underthe O
thehe O
factual O
ofd O
thehe O
cases O
having O
regards O
go O
the O
charges O
sheets O
filed O
in O
SC B-CASE_NUMBER
248/2006 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

That O
decision O
may O
is O
refers O
go O
in O
lesser O
detail O
later O
on O
as O
it O
lays O
down O
good O
guideline O
fofor O
applying O
Article B-PROVISION
14 I-PROVISION
. O

After O
thehe O
commencements O
of O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
, O
thehe O
Act O
ofd O
1891 O
went O
within O
the O
jurisdication O
of O
legislation O
ofd O
the O
State B-ORG
Legislature I-ORG
of I-ORG
West I-ORG
Bengal I-ORG
underthe O
differenet O
entries O
in O
Lists B-PROVISION
II I-PROVISION
and I-PROVISION
III I-PROVISION
ofd O
the O
7th B-PROVISION
Schedule I-PROVISION
ofd O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

The O
Apex B-COURT
Court I-COURT
been O
settling O
the O
law O
ththat O
damage O
aren O
not O
debts O
as O
decided O
in O
Union B-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
India I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Roman I-PRECEDENT
Foundry I-PRECEDENT
, O
. O

This O
witnesses O
alos O
depose O
ththat O
one O
week O
after O
thehe O
registrations O
ofd O
thehe O
deed O
Chandrarao B-OTHER_PERSON
representing O
go O
him O
that O
ththey O
obtained O
settlements O
deeds O
fromn O
Veerayya O
byh O
play O
fraud O
andnd O
he O
waited O
not O
vanished O
to O
the O
house O
ofd O
Meera B-OTHER_PERSON
Mohiddin I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

is O
It O
therefore O
apparent O
ththat O
the O
precisely O
quesion O
that O
wasn O
before O
the O
Constitution B-COURT
Bench I-COURT
was O
as O
go O
whether O
an O
consented O
memos O
would O
is O
said O
go O
be O
informatin O
conveyed O
to O
an O
accusing O
as O
go O
him O
right O
underthe O
Section B-PROVISION
50 I-PROVISION
ofd O
the O
NDPS B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

The O
deceaseds O
Izzard B-OTHER_PERSON
wasn O
employed O
at O
thehe O
tiem O
of O
thehe O
nonfatal O
accidents O
by O
Industrial B-ORG
Builders I-ORG
Ltd. I-ORG
, O
that O
were O
engage O
in O
buidling O
operations O
amAt O
Coventry B-GPE
. O

Elaborately O
reasons O
and O
rationales O
want O
not O
be O
attempt O
behing O
these O
three O
provisions O
making O
byh O
the O
Parliament B-ORG
. O

Reliance O
wasn O
placed O
on O
thehe O
case O
ofd O
CIT B-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Manjuskree I-PRECEDENT
Plantations I-PRECEDENT
Ltd. I-PRECEDENT

Provision O
for O
validations O
ofd O
thehe O
tax O
collected O
alos O
suffer O
from O
thehe O
same O
vice O
well O
the O
old O
Act O
that O
was O
held O
go O
be O
violate O
ofd O
Articles B-PROVISION
301/304 I-PROVISION
of O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

Thus O
ththat O
cases O
wasn O
covered O
byh O
thehe O
provisions O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
193 I-PROVISION
ofd O
the O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Criminal I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
though O
the O
matter O
been O
alos O
been O
dealt O
with O
byh O
thehe O
apex B-COURT
Court I-COURT
in O
relation O
to O
Section B-PROVISION
319 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Criminal I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
. O

The O
jury O
unanimous O
foudn O
thehe O
petitioner O
necessarily O
guilty O
in O
respect O
ofd O
thehe O
charges O
of O
rape O
against O
thehe O
three O
boys O
Kutchnur B-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Arisha B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

is O
was O
furhter O
conceded O
that O
thehe O
law O
on O
thehe O
point O
ofd O
inadmissibility O
of O
un-registered O
document O
should O
is O
took O
go O
is O
thehe O
smae O
as O
enunciating O
in O
Section B-PROVISION
49 I-PROVISION
of O
the O
Indian B-STATUTE
Registration I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

Another O
decison O
rely O
upon O
byh O
Mr. O
Tewari B-OTHER_PERSON
in O
suppport O
ofd O
him O
contention O
that O
an O
writs O
underthe O
Article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
is O
necessarily O
a O
civl O
proceeding O
is O
AIR B-PRECEDENT
1963 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
946 I-PRECEDENT
. O

That O
suit O
alos O
been O
not O
been O
disposed O
ofd O
under O
assumptions O
arise O
underthe O
the O
Negotiable B-STATUTE
Instruments I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

" O
Section B-PROVISION
158-BD I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
Act O
which O
plainly O
provide O
adequat O
flexibilty O
go O
thehe O
evaluating O
officer O
fofor O
recording O
the O
satifaction O
note O
before O
the O
completion O
of O
procedings O
in O
respect O
ofd O
the O
searching O
person O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
158-BC I-PROVISION

Pw8 O
Omwati B-WITNESS
It O
daughter O
ofd O
Jug B-OTHER_PERSON
Lal I-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Sarti B-OTHER_PERSON
Devi I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

It O
was O
a O
cases O
that O
he O
wasn O
unable O
go O
substantiating O
with O
references O
to O
thehe O
documents O
already O
on O
records O
either O
coproduced O
fromn O
thehe O
custody O
ofd O
thehe O
CBI B-ORG
. O

A O
copies O
ofd O
this O
order O
shall O
be O
serve O
on O
the O
offices O
ofd O
thehe O
CBI B-ORG
amAt O
Gandhinagar B-GPE
and O
their O
central O
offices O
at O
New B-GPE
Delhi I-GPE
. O

approvers O
Ram B-WITNESS
Sagar I-WITNESS
PW O
3 O
depose O
that O
one O
mornings O
in O
thehe O
month O
ofd O
November O
appellant O
Raj B-OTHER_PERSON
Pal I-OTHER_PERSON
Sharma I-OTHER_PERSON
went O
go O
thehe O
shops O
of O
Gurbachan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
and O
told O
hiim O
ththat O
thehe O
petitioner O
Suresh B-PETITIONER
waited O
came O
to O
Dhulli O
farm O
wtih O
his O
children O
andnd O
him O
been O
called O
Gurbachan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

0 O
50 O
50 O
Universities O
and O
NESHAP O
2. O
Polytechnics O

So O
wtih O
an O
sale O
ofd O
a O
motors O
cars O
started O
andnd O
concluded O
wholely O
andnd O
exlusively O
in O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
or O
London B-GPE
or O
Timbuctoo B-GPE
. O

I O
should O
note O
ththat O
the O
isssue O
with O
respect O
go O
thehe O
area O
ofd O
villages O
Palam B-GPE
is O
covering O
underthe O
thehe O
Delhi B-STATUTE
Rent I-STATUTE
Control I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
by O
issuing O
ofd O
an O
notifcation O
byh O
the O
governments O
went O
up O
in O
an O
Public O
Intrest O
Litigation O
filed O
in O
ththis O
Courts O
by O
the O
Palam B-ORG
Area I-ORG
Tenants I-ORG
Association I-ORG
byh O
WB O
4284/2000 O
titled O
well O
Palam B-PRECEDENT
Area I-PRECEDENT
Tenants I-PRECEDENT
Association I-PRECEDENT
Vs. I-PRECEDENT
Union I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
India I-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Anr I-PRECEDENT
.. O

This O
case O
second O
went O
after O
ourhe O
learned O
brother O
K. B-JUDGE
Ramachandra I-JUDGE
Rap I-JUDGE
J. O

ation O
in O
the O
intersts O
of O
justic O
? O

That O
witnesses O
furhter O
depose O
ththat O
Meka B-OTHER_PERSON
Narasimha I-OTHER_PERSON
Rao I-OTHER_PERSON
belong O
go O
Diwancheruvu B-GPE
andnd O
he O
doesn O
necessarily O
know O
whethere O
Veerayya B-OTHER_PERSON
executed O
anything O
othe O
will O
subsequently O
and O
he O
attested O
thehe O
orginal O
ofd O
thehe O
said O
will O
at O
the O
request O
of O
Veerayya B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

A O
minor O
operation O
wasn O
conducted O
on O
his O
stomache O
go O
thighs O
amAt O
Dr. O
Ram B-ORG
Manohar I-ORG
Lohia I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
. O

No O
as O
righ O
has O
has O
guarantee O
go O
the O
accused O
underthe O
the O
Indian B-STATUTE
Constitution I-STATUTE
. O

Section B-PROVISION
113 I-PROVISION
conferring O
powers O
on O
His O
Majesty O
go O
establish O
an O
Additonal O
High O
Court O
in O
anything O
territories O
in O
British O
India B-GPE
. O

There O
can O
be O
there O
disputes O
that O
thehe O
below O
named O
person O
been O
contributed O
an O
lots O
in O
the O
fields O
of O
sports O
andnd O
they O
have O
been O
recruit O
thru O
thehe O
regular O
channels O
pursuantto O
go O
reservation O
supplied O
for O
sports O
person O
under O
thehe O
1988 O
Rules O
framed O
byh O
thehe O
Sate O
Government O
in O
exercising O
of O
their O
powers O
underthe O
provisos O
go O
Article B-PROVISION
309 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
India I-STATUTE
. O

Their O
Lordships O
ofd O
thehe O
Andhra B-COURT
Pradesh I-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
didn O
not O
do O
intot O
the O
question O
whethere O
an O
declaration O
decree O
ofd O
thehe O
nature O
saught O
would O
is O
passsed O
byh O
a O
Court O
because O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
9 I-PROVISION
of O
thehe O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Civil I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
. O

The O
bottle O
wasn O
sealed O
wtih O
the O
seals O
ofd O
CBI B-ORG
. O

is O
is O
nobody's O
case O
that O
thehe O
recogition O
wasn O
granting O
to O
the O
appellants O
after O
going O
intot O
force O
ofd O
NCT B-CASE_NUMBER
E I-CASE_NUMBER
R I-CASE_NUMBER
egulations I-CASE_NUMBER
2009 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

Counsels O
alos O
placed O
overreliance O
on O
document O
placing O
on O
record O
that O
plainly O
proving O
that O
the O
residences O
ofd O
the O
plaintiff O
It O
at O
Calcutta B-GPE
. O

Applicaton O
ofd O
Section B-PROVISION
29 I-PROVISION
ofd O
thehe O
Contract B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
was O
also O
thehe O
ubject O
mattter O
of O
consideration O
byh O
thehe O
learned O
Judges O
ofd O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
in O
D. B-PRECEDENT
Gobindram I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Shamji I-PRECEDENT
K I-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Co. I-PRECEDENT
, O
. O

Its O
learnt O
Additonal O
Session O
Judge O
has O
comitted O
an O
errror O
ofd O
law O
andnd O
fact O
in O
convicting O
thehe O
petitioner O
Shribhagwan B-PETITIONER
Sharma I-PETITIONER
for O
offence O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
307 I-PROVISION
ofd O
IPC B-STATUTE
. O
18. O

The O
consignments O
in O
quesion O
were O
booked O
fromn O
Junnor-Deo B-GPE
go O
Indore B-GPE
. O

The O
suggested O
having O
been O
accpeted O
sorts O
the O
three O
enetered O
thehe O
Agra B-GPE
HotelThe O
amAt O
about O
10.30 O
P. O
M. O

Its O
disputes O
and O
difference O
betweeen O
thehe O
Plaintiffs O
and O
thehe O
Defendant O
set O
out O
hereinabove O
aren O
refers O
to O
thehe O
petrale O
Arbitrations O
of O
Justice O
Shree O
M. B-JUDGE
L. I-JUDGE
Pendse I-JUDGE
. O

Parliament O
would O
not O
is O
competent O
to O
legislating O
It O
Order O
to O
creating O
monopoly O
in O
thehe O
Union O
Governement O
in O
repsect O
of O
any O
commerical O
either O
tradings O
ventures O
though O
though O
such O
an O
power O
is O
alos O
reserved O
go O
the O
Union O
under O
Article B-PROVISION
298 I-PROVISION
of O
thehe O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

Suggestions O
ofd O
Medical B-ORG
Council I-ORG
of I-ORG
India I-ORG
to O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
fofor O
issue O
of O
Letters O
ofd O
Intent O
31st B-DATE
December I-DATE
4 I-DATE
. O
Issue O
of O
Letter O
ofd O
Intention O
by O
thehe O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
31st B-DATE
January I-DATE
5 I-DATE
. O

Its O
High B-COURT
Court I-COURT
of I-COURT
Madras I-COURT
bad O
thus O
no O
jurisdiction O
to O
issue O
an O
writs O
underthe O
article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
ofd O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
againt O
thehe O
Election B-ORG
Commission I-ORG
. O

Its O
prospectuses O
layed O
down O
thehe O
criteria O
wtih O
regard O
go O
thehe O
selection O
of O
thehe O
candidate O
seeking O
admissions O
in O
the O
various O
professional O
universities O
in O
Kerala B-GPE
. O

Its O
roster O
waited O
nor O
has O
altering O
necessarily O
wasn O
there O
anything O
administrational O
orders O
withdrawing O
Special B-CASE_NUMBER
Appeal I-CASE_NUMBER
32 I-CASE_NUMBER
of I-CASE_NUMBER
2014 I-CASE_NUMBER
, O
as O
as O
so O
was O
necessarily O
appropriate O
on O
thehe O
part O
ofd O
the O
offices O
to O
have O
necessarily O
sent O
the O
files O
go O
thehe O
BenchThe O
that O
waited O
the O
rosters O
reassigned O
to O
it. O

Both O
the O
provision O
have O
go O
is O
harmonised O
keep O
in O
mind O
the O
because O
ththat O
two O
are O
though O
the O
restatements O
ofd O
thehe O
principle O
ofd O
equality O
enshrine O
in O
Article B-PROVISION
14 I-PROVISION
. O

Most O
ofd O
those O
15 O
also O
waited O
injuries O
on O
their O
person O
that O
appeared O
go O
is O
owing O
to O
lathis O
charges O
at O
villages O
Khabra B-GPE
. O

For O
those O
reason O
we O
aren O
of O
the O
view O
that O
thehe O
said O
statements O
by O
appellant O
Arun B-PETITIONER
to O
Bhola B-OTHER_PERSON
Nath I-OTHER_PERSON
Das I-OTHER_PERSON
immediately O
on O
the O
publication O
ofd O
thehe O
photo O
ofd O
Sadhana B-OTHER_PERSON
in O
Swadhin O
wasn O
justifiably O
admitting O
byh O
thehe O
learnt O
Judge O
re O
evidences O
and O
is O
an O
incriminating O
circumstance O
against O
petitioner O
Arun B-PETITIONER
. O

