My O
own O
anxious O
but O
critical O
response O
to O
this O
argument O
but O
I O
fear O
the O
failure O
to O
make O
it. O

Both O
above O
decisions O
have O
be O
challenged O
under O
the O
ground O
that O
application O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
6 I-PROVISION
in O
a O
Land B-STATUTE
Acquisition I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
ended O
at O
expiry O
of O
one O
month O
from O
the O
date O
published O
in O
Section B-PROVISION
4 I-PROVISION
. O

counsel O
that O
important O
documents O
and O
information O
are O
deliberately O
hidden O
from O
a O
listed O
firm O
in O
that O
a O
call O
to O
offer O
and O
a O
statement O
about O
its O
Board's O
election O
of O
May O
2 O
were O
both O
posted O
only O
on O
April O
27. O

Section O
30 O
of O
the O
judgment O
on O
a O
case O
against O
Sabita B-OTHER_PERSON
Prasad I-OTHER_PERSON
was O
quoted O
as O
- O

Let O
me O
consider O
in O
a O
minute O
another O
similar O
situation O
when O
a O
Trial O
Court O
had O
granted O
an O
ex O
hoc O
in O
quest O
injunction O
and O
the O
defendant O
of O
this O
case O
had O
a O
motion O
challenging O
both O
an O
existing O
injunction O
an O
action O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
45 I-PROVISION
. O

His O
house O
with O
the O
two O
uncles O
Nathuram B-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Prem B-OTHER_PERSON
was O
just O
adjacent O
to O
his O
field O
after O
being O
informant O
by O
their O
father O
Hariram B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

During O
that O
same O
year O
1978 O
she O
bought O
upon O
acres O
to O
gair O
al O
land O
located O
in O
the O
State B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bihar I-ORG
at O
the O
Bagra B-GPE
of O
the O
district O
of O
Gopalganj B-GPE
, O

The O
control O
over O
all O
the O
activities O
was O
turned O
over O
to O
a O
Raj-pramukh B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

An O
additional O
provision O
that O
is O
cited O
to O
aid O
in O
the O
accused O
is O
Section B-PROVISION
7 I-PROVISION
of O
the O
Guide O
to O
Indian O
Extradition O
offences O
appearing O
under O
an O
Indian B-STATUTE
Extradition I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
1903 I-STATUTE
. O
16. O

he O
market O
s O
the O
property O
of O
the O
public O

The O
participants O
of O
the O
specified O
Oudh B-GPE
areas O
were O
expected O
to O
have O
held O
at O
Lucknow B-GPE
. O

This O
petitioner O
has O
23 O
months O
s O
working O
experience O
on O
stage O
carriages O
but O
also O
experience O
on O
the O
road O
section O
of O
these O
two O
road O
in O
question O
which O
is O
the O
major O
est O
routes O
in O
the O
Palghat B-GPE
district I-GPE
. O

These O
may O
include O
cases O
where O
in O
the O
delay O
of O
much O
more O
time O
can O
be O
found O
they O
prove O
wrong O
and O
refuse O
relief O
from O
a O
claim O
in O
Article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
of O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

The O
most O
valuable O
player O
was O
certainly O
Keshar B-WITNESS
Singh I-WITNESS
. O

Before O
I O
get O
to O
another O
contention O
by O
Mr. O
Narendra B-OTHER_PERSON
Mohan I-OTHER_PERSON
Kasliwal I-OTHER_PERSON
in O
respect O
to O
increase O
of O
the O
grade O
s O
for O
entry O
to O
State O
Colleges O
of O
21 O
year O
to O
22 O
year O
we O
consider O
necessary O
that O
we O
deal O
about O
these O
first O
two O
types O
of O
issues O
that O
have O
been O
challenged O
from O
Mr. O
Mridul B-OTHER_PERSON
with O
relation O
al O
issues O
attacked O
by O
Mr. O
Narendra B-OTHER_PERSON
Mohan I-OTHER_PERSON
Kasliwal I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

Under O
these O
circumstances O
the O
Court O
held O
no O
interest O
was O
taken O
in O
the O
payment O
or O
gift O
which O
was O
given O
to O
the O
State O
Under O
Section B-PROVISION
240 I-PROVISION
. O
24. O

During O
that O
very O
time O
Mahendra B-OTHER_PERSON
Pal I-OTHER_PERSON
shot O
out O
of O
the O
Kothari O
in O
a O
south-east O
direction O
which O
Bala O
Pal O
also O
shot O
at O
and O
Bala O
fell O
out O
in O
a O
street O
and O
got O
hit O
with O
Banka B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

An O
additional O
Clause B-PROVISION
VIII I-PROVISION
postulates O
the O
application O
an O
import O
tax O
of O
its O
highest O
possible O
level O
for O
those O
products O
which O
are O
exempt O
under O
more O
than O
one O
of O
these O
rules O
of O
Schedule B-PROVISION
IV I-PROVISION
. O

ion O
to O
proceed O
to O
this O
banner O

Similar O
regulations O
are O
issued O
for O
other O
co-sharers O
of O
the O
Noori B-ORG
Sugar I-ORG
Works I-ORG
. O

He O
is O
treated O
at O
Allahabad B-GPE
Hospital O
Lucknow B-GPE
. O

Nachhatar B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
wife O
of O
Sadhu B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
resident O
in O
Bathinda O
Road O
Hindaiya O
District B-GPE
Sangrur I-GPE
. O
... O
It O
s O
1- O
Mukhtiar B-OTHER_PERSON
Kaur I-OTHER_PERSON
mother O
of O
Surjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
daughter O
of O
Harnam B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
2- O
Surjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
father O
of O
Harnam B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
or O
3- O
Karnail B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
daughter O
and O
Surjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
residents O
in O
Road O
Golewala B-GPE
. O

He O
said O
the O
late O
Bhausaheb B-OTHER_PERSON
would O
take O
his O
own O
vehicle O
to O
visit O
the O
shop O
of O
Badrimama B-GPE
. O

Any O
modification O
has O
been O
made O
by O
this O
Government O
with O
respect O
of O
laws O
of O
Article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
of O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
India I-STATUTE
. O

Mary O
followed O
her O
father O
took O
a O
bus O
and O
reached O
a O
village O
just O
over O
the O
bridge O
and O
where O
she O
took O
a O
south O
bound O
train O
which O
arrived O
in O
Contai B-GPE
. O
Page O
9. O

They O
followed O
it O
for O
long O
but O
he O
did O
not O
find O
Munni B-OTHER_PERSON
Bai I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

The O
reasons O
that O
I O
have O
already O
mentioned O
I O
respectfully O
dissent O
against O
the O
decision O
being O
taken O
in O
this O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

The O
companies O
worry O
about O
the O
maintainability O
for O
a O
claim O
form O
and O
locus O
ability O
of O
potential O
claimants O
to O
complete O
it. O

On O
landing O
in O
India B-GPE
, O
he O
considered O
himself O
for O
refugees O
having O
complied O
to O
several O
administrative O
formalities O
necessary O
for O
a O
migrant O
from O
Sri B-GPE
Lanka I-GPE
. O

The O
incident O
is O
reported O
may O
have O
happened O
at O
Bombay B-GPE
- O
Pune B-GPE
Highway O
near O
Nalgaon B-GPE
Village I-GPE
, O
in O
a O
the O
direction O
of O
Wadagaon-Moval B-ORG
Police I-ORG
Station I-ORG
. O

Anand O
had O
participated O
on O
the O
chase O
team O
in O
his O
search O
of O
7 O
people O
at O
village O
Chandrahatti B-GPE
, O
who O
had O
been O
He O
also O
came O
from O
Hajipur B-GPE
and O
found O
that O
15 O
persons O
were O
being O
held O
up O
by O
the O
Anand B-PETITIONER
Mohan I-PETITIONER
or O
Lovely B-PETITIONER
Anand I-PETITIONER
. O

The O
Petitioners O
refer O
red O
to O
either O
Madhya B-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
District I-ORG
Police I-ORG
Force I-ORG
or O
the O
Madhya B-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
special I-ORG
Armed I-ORG
Force I-ORG
. O

Dr. O
N. B-OTHER_PERSON
M. I-OTHER_PERSON
Ghatate I-OTHER_PERSON
as O
Respondent O
in O
CA. B-CASE_NUMBER
1658/80 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

every O
aspect O
of O
it. O

The O
first O
example O
was O
the O
judgment O
by O
Indian O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
in O
Bimal B-PRECEDENT
Chandra I-PRECEDENT
Banerjee I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
State I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
Madhya I-PRECEDENT
Pradesh I-PRECEDENT
AIR I-PRECEDENT
1959 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
169 I-PRECEDENT
. O

Sureshwar B-OTHER_PERSON
Jha I-OTHER_PERSON
was O
placed O
at O
Rahman B-OTHER_PERSON
's O
Nursing O
Hospital O
and O
after O
there O
she O
was O
taken O
into O
Patna B-GPE
. O

It O
is O
this O
attitude O
which O
is O
evident O
in O
the O
cases O
submitted O
before O
this O
Constitution B-COURT
Bench I-COURT
. O

This O
was O
followed O
with O
Mr. O
Som B-OTHER_PERSON
Nath I-OTHER_PERSON
Iyer I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
learned O
member O
of O
the O
respondent O
s O
at O
Civil B-CASE_NUMBER
Appeal I-CASE_NUMBER
2317 I-CASE_NUMBER
of I-CASE_NUMBER
1972 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

Earlier O
its O
title O
is O
Chowdhry B-ORG
Plast I-ORG
Ltd. I-ORG

You O
have O
also O
a O
benefit O
of O
hearing O
to O
make O
my O
judgment O
of O
my O
own O
opinion O
Chinnappa B-JUDGE
Reddy I-JUDGE
, O
J. O

Second O
proviso O
of O
section B-PROVISION
143 I-PROVISION
in O
Civil O
Constitution O
Act O
1881 O
set O
out O
two O
options O
to O
try O
a O
case O
in O
a O
trial O
court O
and O
other O
order O
given O
under O
CrPC B-STATUTE
. O

Her O
husband O
is O
employed O
in O
Delhi B-GPE
so O
she O
can O
only O
have O
expected O
to O
keep O
the O
secret O
to O
try O
and O
win O
over O
the O
affection O
or O
confidence O
from O
his O
daughter O
in O
his O
parent's O
house O
in O
Aligarh B-GPE
. O

and O
paid O
a O
requisite O
amount O
till O
last O
quarter O
of O
31st B-DATE
March I-DATE
1974 I-DATE
. O

The O
actions O
in O
administrative O
court O
are O
brought O
against O
an O
opinion O
made O
by O
a O
District O
Court O
of O
a O
Karnataka B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
summarily O
rejecting O
the O
s O
lings O
of O
the O
students O
against O
a O
summary O
decision O
delivered O
under O
Justice O
Rama B-JUDGE
Jois I-JUDGE
on O
two O
separate O
petitions O
brought O
by O
students O
challenging O
the O
conditions O
of O
the O
admission O
to O
the O
Karnataka B-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

Chief O
among O
them O
was O
Simranjit B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
Mann I-OTHER_PERSON
who O
has O
recently O
released O
from O
Central O
Indian B-ORG
Police I-ORG
Service I-ORG
. O

Only O
these O
principles O
and O
common O
law O
must O
determine O
the O
decisions O
of O
our O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
, O
for O
they O
must O
entertain O
the O
question O
of O
Article B-PROVISION
32 I-PROVISION
only O
as O
an O
enforcement O
of O
authority O
established O
in O
Part B-PROVISION
III I-PROVISION
in O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

K. B-OTHER_PERSON
B. I-OTHER_PERSON
Asthana I-OTHER_PERSON
for O
Indian O
State B-GPE
of I-GPE
Uttar I-GPE
Pradesh I-GPE
. O

Police O
Commissioner O
and O
Assistant O
Commissioner O
Chepauk B-GPE
Chennai-600 I-GPE
005 O
3. O

Article B-PROVISION
246 I-PROVISION
and O
Title O
I O
confer O
a O
specific O
authority O
upon O
Parliament B-ORG
. O

It O
appears O
based O
on O
its O
usage O
in O
the O
words O
that O
other O
case O
was O
in O
place O
that O
made O
both O
parties O
appear O
in O
the O
Supreme O
Court O
and O
that O
a O
false O
language O
is O
used O
against O
the O
CBI B-ORG
in O
its O
affidavit O
submitted O
with O
this O
High O
Court O
with O
the O
intent O
to O
deny O
any O
allegation O
made O
in O
the O
original O
petitioners O

They O
were O
therefore O
bound O
to O
follow O
this O
final O
judgment O
by O
the O
Constitution B-COURT
Bench I-COURT
. O

He O
also O
has O
said O
how O
his O
Local O
Government O
approached O
his O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
before O
taking O
decision O
of O
approach O
the O
Government O
for O
giving O
of O
a O
requisite O
notice O
because O
he O
was O
of O
the O
opinion O
how O
the O
notice O
should O
been O
given O
through O
the O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
. O

The O
news O
is O
good O
news O
to O
the O
Jagpal B-PETITIONER
. O

Mr. O
Joshi B-OTHER_PERSON
comments O
upon O
the O
judgment O
by O
a O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
in O
Commissioner B-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
Income-tax I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Kumbakonam I-PRECEDENT
Mutual I-PRECEDENT
Benefit I-PRECEDENT
Fund I-PRECEDENT
Ltd. I-PRECEDENT

Our O
General O
Counsel O
in O
this O
case O
submitted O
why O
he O
would O
prefer O
a O
position O
held O
by O
Shivashankar B-JUDGE
Bhat I-JUDGE
, O
J. O
on O
the O
case O
against O
Balappa B-OTHER_PERSON
in O
comparison O
to O
the O
views O
held O
in O
Swami B-JUDGE
, O
J. O
which O
were O
affirmed O
in O
a O
case O
against O
Gwalior B-OTHER_PERSON
Rayon I-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Delhi O
Division O
Court O
in O
the O
cases O
against O
Lakshmi B-OTHER_PERSON
Bai I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

It O
will O
have O
taught O
to O
the O
wife O
and O
the O
man O
which O
was O
served O
as O
a O
Professor O
in O
City B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chicago I-ORG
. O

They O
were O
several O
from O
these O
Tribunals O
in O
our O
State B-ORG
of I-ORG
Madhya I-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
but O
their O
central O
centres O
are O
in O
our O
State B-ORG
of I-ORG
Madhya I-ORG
Pradesh I-ORG
. O

The O
findings O
were O
either O
opposed O
to O
science O
and O
law O
or O
not O
to O
proper O
foreign O
policy O
for O
India B-GPE
. O

Both O
the O
dates O
fall O
on O
the O
Ghaziabad B-GPE
. O

An O
airport O
officer O
alongwith O
two O
airport O
employees O
then O
and O
again O
left O
a O
prepaid O
car O
parking O
lot O
of O
the O
IGI B-ORG
Airport I-ORG
. O

My O
husband O
is O
a O
judge O
practicing O
at O
Supreme O
Court O
so O
much O
as O
in O
Delhi B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

A O
petitioner's O
family O
originally O
resided O
at O
Umreth B-GPE
, O
while O
the O
actual O
place O
at O
birth O
for O
a O
child O
was O
Vaso B-GPE
. O

A O
learned O
lawyer O
from O
the O
government O
informed O
us O
this O
case O
is O
still O
not O
considered O
for O
the O
large O
majority O
in O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

That O
is O
a O
decision O
of O
Santosh B-JUDGE
, O
J. O
A O
whom O
I O
had O
referred O
to O
before O
on O
this O
issue O
of O
Laxmimanojana B-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Sujnandra I-PRECEDENT
. O

Onkar B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
Lakhawat I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
the O
judge O
further O
said O
that O
the O
failure O
by O
appellant O
Sohani B-PETITIONER
to O
prevent O
an O
attack O
has O
been O
taken O
as O
excuse O
and O
found O
her O
guilty O
for O
crime O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
302 I-PROVISION
in O
Indian O
IPC B-STATUTE
. O

They O
read O
the O
statement O
of O
Officer O
Ashok B-OTHER_PERSON
Kumar I-OTHER_PERSON
Jain I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
abductee O
Vikash B-OTHER_PERSON
Jain I-OTHER_PERSON
aur O
Jai O
Prakash B-WITNESS
Singh I-WITNESS
under O
Section B-PROVISION
161 I-PROVISION
of O
CrPC B-STATUTE
. O

This O
punishment O
is O
severe O
as O
the O
offence O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
354 I-PROVISION
IPC B-STATUTE
was O
made O
the O
non-bailable O
one O
for O
this O
State O
of O
Andhra B-GPE
Pradesh I-GPE
. O

The O
other O
parts O
of O
the O
Second O
Schedule O
of O
this O
schedule O
apply O
to O
applications O
by O
International O
Arbitration B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
and O
make O
for O
some O
cases O
exception O
to O
applications O
by O
International O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Criminal I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
. O

Let O
us O
now O
return O
to O
our O
topic O
in O
P. O
W. O
5 O
Somnath B-WITNESS
Sen. I-WITNESS

THE O
NEW O
KVC B-ORG
BANK I-ORG
MUGAD I-ORG
BRANCH I-ORG
TQ I-ORG
& I-ORG
DIST I-ORG
: I-ORG
DHARWAD I-ORG
28. O

The O
spokesman O
of O
a O
religious O
community O
who O
deposed O
Deface O
ment O
Constitution O
was O
the O
R. B-OTHER_PERSON
S. I-OTHER_PERSON
Gavai I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
Speaker O
to O
a O
Maharashtra B-ORG
State I-ORG
Legislative I-ORG
Council I-ORG
. O

After O
completion O
the O
interview O
he O
has O
submitted O
his O
following O
documents O
to O
the O
court O
for O
criminal O
charges O
required O
by O
Sections B-PROVISION
376 I-PROVISION
and I-PROVISION
420 I-PROVISION
of O
IPC B-STATUTE
. O
5. O

There O
is O
clear O
on O
one O
end O
of O
these O
arguments O
before O
the O
Sales B-COURT
Tax I-COURT
Tribunal I-COURT
the O
money O
from O
those O
entries O
that O
were O
made O
on O
the O
khata O
of O
Jayantilal B-ORG
Thakordas I-ORG
& I-ORG
Co. I-ORG
, O
in O
charges O
against O
the O
Angadia B-OTHER_PERSON
, O
were O
actually O
debit O
ed O
from O
the O
account O
s O
of O
an O
assessee-firm O
without O
having O
been O
given O
by O
that O
assessee-firm O
to O
an O
Angadia B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

The O
decision O
of O
an O
Income-tax O
Tribunal O
is O
approved O
by O
a O
Pull O
Bench O
in O
a O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

Their O
members O
in O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
also O
recently O
approved O
these O
above O
recommendations O
by O
a O
decision O
reported O
at O
AIR B-PRECEDENT
1957 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
912 I-PRECEDENT
. O
66. O

Both O
accused O
were O
caught O
attacking O
PW2 O
in O
Baiju B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

Therefore O
this O
I O
did O
indeed O
see O
any O
force O
in O
the O
arguments O
made O
by O
the O
defense O
counsel O
for O
my O
case O
and O
gave O
court O
the O
right O
of O
exercise O
the O
presumption O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
139 I-PROVISION
in O
this O
NI B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

This O
collision O
took O
off O
approximately O
nine O
miles O
outside O
Bhatia B-GPE
towards O
Dwarka B-GPE
between O
1.30 O
to O
1.45 O
P. O
M. O

Actor O
Manjunath B-OTHER_PERSON
Ithal I-OTHER_PERSON
was O
at O
Sweet O
Party O
at O
Shimoga B-GPE
. O

In O
the O
statement O
made O
in O
favor O
by O
the O
company O
it O
is O
said O
only O
with O
respect O
of O
the O
purchases O
made O
from O
Calcutta B-GPE
the O
articles O
of O
which O
are O
sent O
via O
air O
to O
Madras B-GPE
. O

The O
mass O
was O
carried O
by O
the O
autorickshaw O
to O
various O
cities O
until O
finally O
brought O
into O
Kuthirakadavu B-GPE
. O

These O
Insurance O
companies O
also O
failed O
to O
explain O
why O
it O
had O
taken O
the O
premium O
of O
the O
driver O
as O
their O
maximum O
limit O
of O
policy O
is O
not O
allowed O
by O
Section B-PROVISION
147 I-PROVISION
of O
Motor B-STATUTE
Vehicle I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

The O
judge O
held O
that O
Section B-PROVISION
163­A I-PROVISION
was O
not O
making O
any O
deviation O
of O
the O
civil O
criminal O
liability O
of O
a O
victim O
of O
suicide O
but O
was O
a O
violation O
of O
the O
requirements O
of O
the O
Fatal B-STATUTE
Accidents I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

The O
Kameswar B-PRECEDENT
Prosad I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
State I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
Bihar I-PRECEDENT
or O
O. B-PRECEDENT
K. I-PRECEDENT
Ghose I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Ex I-PRECEDENT
Joseph I-PRECEDENT
Court O
s O
also O
found O
out O
the O
freedom O
to O
vote O
was O
not O
a O
fundamental O
right O
protected O
by O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

This O
same O
case O
was O
subsequently O
closed O
by O
this O
same O
decision O
in O
Reckitt B-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Colman I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
India I-PRECEDENT
Ltd. I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
CIT I-PRECEDENT
. O

Thereafter O
both O
police O
from O
each O
party O
did O
a O
through O
search O
of O
the O
house O
with O
two O
independent O
s O
, O
the O
wife O
of O
chief O
minister O
of O
the O
government O
, O
Mr. O
Jayaprakash B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

The O
compensatory O
charge O
falls O
outside O
of O
law O
under O
article B-PROVISION
301 I-PROVISION
if O
the O
land O
is O
used O
for O
create O
opportunities O
for O
trade O
to O
promote O
a O
free-flow O
of O
capital O
and O
nothing O
can O
impede O
it. O

I O
have O
directed O
a O
copie O
from O
that O
document O
to O
being O
sent O
to O
my O
fourth O
respondent O
Subodh B-RESPONDENT
Chandra I-RESPONDENT
Bose I-RESPONDENT
. O

This O
same O
would O
not O
been O
in O
one O
single O
decision O
in O
that O
said O
district O
and O
in O
the O
view O
of O
all O
other O
cases O
functioning O
in O
the O
districts O
related O
to O
the O
District O
Court O
in O
Madurai B-GPE
are O
subordinate O
cases O
under O
a O
Principal O
Court O
in O
Chennai B-GPE
. O

This O
High O
Tribunal O
negatived O
the O
claims O
which O
the O
sought O
parties O
have O
raised O
before O
the O
Tribunal O
also O
has O
convicted O
each O
of O
the O
accused O
men O
for O
the O
offence O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
302 I-PROVISION
subject O
to O
Section B-PROVISION
149 I-PROVISION
of O
an O
Indian B-STATUTE
Penal I-STATUTE
Code I-STATUTE
. O
5. O

In O
AIR B-PRECEDENT
1954 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
39 I-PRECEDENT
, O
the O
reports O
were O
that O
the O
dacoity O
had O
was O
found O
at O
his O
home O
by O
Mr O
Namdeo B-OTHER_PERSON
Moti I-OTHER_PERSON
Ram I-OTHER_PERSON
in O
late O
afternoon O
of O
Friday O
11th B-DATE
of I-DATE
December I-DATE
1950 I-DATE
. O

This O
seems O
odd O
how O
and O
how O
the O
government O
can O
claim O
any O
of O
the O
recommendations O
of O
a O
Prime O
Minister O
in O
India B-GPE
or O
Chief O
Justice O
of O
Delhi B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

It O
clearly O
results O
from O
Section O
4.6 O
of O
Article O
III O
and O
Schedule O
I O
in O
the O
Constitution O
of O
a O
Fourth B-ORG
Central I-ORG
Pay I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
that O
this O
Committee O
could O
not O
undertake O
a O
full O
investigation O
of O
these O
various O
parts O
and O
different O
functions O
of O
a O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

The O
family O
Kaki B-PETITIONER
and O
Har B-PETITIONER
Kaur I-PETITIONER
filed O
the O
application O
for O
the O
possession O
of O
real O
estate O
by O
Mr O
Chanan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

and O
the O
amount O
is O
required O
by O
the O
law O
and O
make O
the O
annual O
contribution O
up O
until O
the O
limit O
prescribed O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
6 I-PROVISION
. O

A O
power O
of O
legislate O
with O
respect O
to O
this O
comes O
to O
the O
Parliament B-ORG
under O
Entires B-PROVISION
10 I-PROVISION
and I-PROVISION
14 I-PROVISION
of I-PROVISION
List I-PROVISION
I I-PROVISION
of I-PROVISION
the I-PROVISION
Seventh I-PROVISION
Schedule I-PROVISION
. O

Into O
this O
long O
chain O
of O
ties O
beginning O
with O
the O
Constitution O
Act O
was O
fitted O
Article B-PROVISION
141 I-PROVISION
that O
gave O
by O
the O
power O
of O
veto O
of O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
the O
binding O
supremacy O
over O
any O
territory O
in O
India B-GPE
. O

Similarly O
where O
a O
man O
misuses O
and O
or O
takes O
an O
object O
not O
attached O
with O
his O
partner O
from O
their O
matrimonial O
home O
it O
hardly O
comes O
into O
an O
ambit O
of O
criminality O
in O
Section B-PROVISION
406 I-PROVISION
, O
Indian B-STATUTE
Penal I-STATUTE
Code I-STATUTE
. O

Respondent O
Pradeep B-RESPONDENT
also O
stated O
how O
he O
was O
in O
college O
in O
NOIDA B-ORG
which O
is O
residing O
close O
to O
his O
father O
Kuldeep B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

Suresh O
Raj B-PETITIONER
Pal I-PETITIONER
tried O
to O
remove O
his O
head O
and O
did O
not O
and O
then O
Gurbachan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
took O
the O
large O
head O
and O
by O
some O
help O
of O
others O
he O
put O
the O
human O
body O
into O
the O
sceptic O
box O
situated O
on O
the O
south O
side O
in O
his O
bungalow O
s O
with O
Suresh B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

On O
this O
view O
see O
Naren B-PRECEDENT
Anappa I-PRECEDENT
Shethi I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Jayantilal I-PRECEDENT
Shah I-PRECEDENT
, O
. O

Sudesh B-OTHER_PERSON
had O
concealed O
a O
rifle O
or O
pistol O
of O
the O
name O
Uhlawas B-GPE
at O
his O
house O
of O
which O
he O
knows O
and O
everyone O
also O
knew O
of O
it. O

The O
rights O
for O
teachers O
appointed O
already O
are O
limited O
by O
a O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

The O
lands O
were O
Government O
property O
es O
the O
Indian O
Government O
have O
no O
right O
to O
sell O
of O
same O
for O
Neyveli B-ORG
Lignite I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
. O

Out O
of O
this O
inquiry O
there O
is O
found O
the O
deceased O
Jug B-OTHER_PERSON
Lal I-OTHER_PERSON
is O
Major O
of O
Army O
and O
had O
married O
Sarti B-OTHER_PERSON
Devi I-OTHER_PERSON
but O
in O
1950 O
Sarti B-OTHER_PERSON
Devi I-OTHER_PERSON
left O
with O
one O
daughter O
Omvati B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

In O
considering O
a O
judgment O
passed O
in O
National B-ORG
& I-ORG
Grindlays I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
which O
was O
based O
upon O
a O
ratio O
given O
by O
a O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
on O
Jugraj B-PRECEDENT
Singh I-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Another I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
jaswant I-PRECEDENT
Singh I-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Others I-PRECEDENT
, O
this O
decision O
changed O
some O
provisions O
in O
Sections B-PROVISION
11 I-PROVISION
& I-PROVISION
14 I-PROVISION
in O
a O
Notaries B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

After O
our O
Constitution B-STATUTE
came O
into O
effect O
the O
lot O
more O
cases O
has O
been O
brought O
before O
our O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
with O
regard O
to O
Article B-PROVISION
311 I-PROVISION
. O

This O
is O
the O
view O
of O
the O
petitioners O
as O
Section B-PROVISION
33 I-PROVISION
in O
the O
VAT B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
does O
not O
provide O
for O
the O
VAT O
according O
to O
Entry B-STATUTE
Tax I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

or O
even O
some O
days O
or O
maybe O
even O
couple O
weeks O
before O
it. O

In O
the O
instance O
there O
was O
not O
being O
established O
by O
the O
court O
that O
both O
plaintiffs O
are O
residents O
of O
India B-GPE
at O
any O
time O
under O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

A O
Second O
Circuit O
in O
a O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
held O
how O
an O
Executive O
Order O
does O
indeed O
trench O
into O
an O
executive O
power O
s O
the O
Federal O
Legislature O
and O
that O
observations O
quoted O
above O
are O
made O
in O
upholding O
a O
judgment O
of O
the O
Madras B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

Mohmed B-OTHER_PERSON
Ahmed I-OTHER_PERSON
Manjoti I-OTHER_PERSON
has O
driven O
the O
road O
of O
village O
Palia B-GPE
to O
Ahmedabad B-GPE
with O
side O
Alimohmed B-OTHER_PERSON
Bhara I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
Arvind B-OTHER_PERSON
Bhailal I-OTHER_PERSON
, O
Babu B-OTHER_PERSON
alias I-OTHER_PERSON
Babla I-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Ali O
Ibrahim B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

P. O
W. O
1 O
said O
by O
his O
mother O
that O
by O
now O
she O
did O
already O
understand O
that O
his O
father O
is O
T. B-OTHER_PERSON
Hanumantha I-OTHER_PERSON
Rao I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

But O
generally O
a O
loan O
in O
that O
instance O
is O
one O
drawn O
from O
a O
western O
bank O
if O
the O
payment O
by O
a O
foreign O
bank O
is O
made O
within O
any O
territory O
of O
India B-GPE
. O

This O
case O
have O
now O
be O
settled O
by O
US O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

A O
conductor O
is O
asked O
to O
present O
Conductor's O
licence O
and O
current O
driving O
track O
record O
as O
restriction O
of O
the O
Regulations O
as O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
45 I-PROVISION
of O
Kerala O
State B-STATUTE
Road I-STATUTE
Transport I-STATUTE
Corporation I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

He O
also O
referred O
back O
to O
focused O
on O
the O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
decision O
of O
Mahasay B-PRECEDENT
Ganesh I-PRECEDENT
Prasad I-PRECEDENT
Ray I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Narendra I-PRECEDENT
Nath I-PRECEDENT
Sen I-PRECEDENT
AIR I-PRECEDENT
1953 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
431 I-PRECEDENT
the O
light O
of O
his O
proposition O
that O
such O
financial O
reports O
themselves O
should O
not O
have O
considered O
financial O
accounts O
within O
the O
context O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
90 I-PROVISION
in O
Financial O
Evidence B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

It O
is O
writ O
large O
as O
the O
issues O
had O
appeared O
and O
been O
kept O
at O
bay O
by O
the O
orders O
from O
the O
Hon'ble O
Delhi B-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
with O
subsequent O
resolution O
of O
this O
case O
from O
the O
Hon'ble O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
. O

There O
was O
not O
mentioned O
in O
this O
above O
judgment O
of O
Hon'ble O
High O
Tribunal O
whether O
there O
was O
a O
notification O
by O
which O
this O
DRC B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
has O
not O
passed O
into O
the O
District O
of O
Delhi B-GPE
that O
is O
also O
a O
Sub O
Division O
of O
West O
Delhi B-GPE
, O
Village O
Najafgarh B-GPE
. O

c. O
An O
order O
framed O
under O
SC B-CASE_NUMBER
254/2006 I-CASE_NUMBER
should O
be O
made O
for O
compliance O
with O
law O
under O
the O
circumstances O
in O
this O
case O
having O
regard O
for O
the O
charges O
as O
set O
under O
SC B-CASE_NUMBER
248/2006 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

This O
article O
may O
be O
refer O
towards O
in O
more O
details O
further O
down O
and O
this O
lays O
out O
good O
guidelines O
on O
applying O
Article B-PROVISION
14 I-PROVISION
. O

At O
its O
commencement O
of O
this O
Constitution B-STATUTE
, O
this O
law O
of O
1891 O
came O
under O
a O
power O
to O
legislation O
of O
a O
State B-ORG
Legislature I-ORG
of I-ORG
West I-ORG
Bengal I-ORG
under O
the O
authority O
of O
Lists B-PROVISION
II I-PROVISION
and I-PROVISION
III I-PROVISION
of O
the O
7th B-PROVISION
Schedule I-PROVISION
to O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

An O
Apex B-COURT
Court I-COURT
judge O
established O
the O
case O
where O
damages O
are O
not O
equal O
and O
decided O
in O
Union B-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
India I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Roman I-PRECEDENT
Foundry I-PRECEDENT
, O
. O

It O
was O
also O
true O
because O
the O
day O
before O
his O
registration O
for O
these O
deeds O
Chandrarao B-OTHER_PERSON
represented O
told O
him O
how O
he O
obtained O
the O
money O
from O
Veerayya O
by O
playing O
fraud O
that O
they O
have O
now O
gone O
to O
the O
court O
with O
Meera B-OTHER_PERSON
Mohiddin I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

This O
is O
not O
apparent O
how O
a O
key O
question O
which O
stood O
before O
the O
Constitution B-COURT
Bench I-COURT
was O
related O
to O
whether O
a O
registration O
form O
could O
been O
considered O
to O
contain O
consent O
conveyed O
by O
an O
individual O
according O
to O
the O
requirements O
in O
Section B-PROVISION
50 I-PROVISION
of O
an O
NDPS B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

Army O
general O
Izzard B-OTHER_PERSON
is O
employed O
in O
his O
time O
for O
this O
mass O
shooting O
by O
Industrial B-ORG
Builders I-ORG
Ltd. I-ORG
, O
which O
was O
engaged O
in O
construction O
operations O
at O
Coventry B-GPE
. O

Some O
reason O
ing O
logic O
seems O
to O
have O
attempted O
in O
these O
two O
provisions O
made O
in O
this O
Parliament B-ORG
. O

Focus O
is O
placed O
upon O
the O
case O
in O
CIT B-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Manjuskree I-PRECEDENT
Plantations I-PRECEDENT
Ltd. I-PRECEDENT

Issue O
of O
validation O
of O
income O
taxes O
collected O
here O
came O
from O
this O
same O
vice O
as O
the O
tax O
law O
which O
was O
considered O
to O
a O
violation O
to O
Articles B-PROVISION
301/304 I-PROVISION
in O
our O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

Therefore O
the O
matter O
is O
brought O
under O
the O
provision O
in O
Section B-PROVISION
193 I-PROVISION
in O
the O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Criminal I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
but O
that O
matter O
had O
also O
been O
deal O
led O
by O
an O
apex B-COURT
Court I-COURT
in O
relation O
with O
Section B-PROVISION
319 I-PROVISION
of O
that O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Criminal I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
. O

The O
jury O
also O
held O
the O
appellant O
not O
innocent O
in O
respect O
to O
a O
case O
for O
murder O
of O
two O
young O
women O
Kutchnur B-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Arisha B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

He O
was O
also O
told O
the O
Indian O
law O
on O
this O
point O
of O
view O
of O
un-registered O
documents O
had O
been O
taken O
as O
mean O
that O
same O
as O
found O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
49 I-PROVISION
of O
an O
Indian B-STATUTE
Registration I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

The O
case O
relied O
on O
for O
Mr. O
Tewari B-OTHER_PERSON
and O
favor O
ing O
his O
argument O
that O
the O
investigation O
under O
Article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
was O
not O
a O
criminal O
proceeding O
is O
AIR B-PRECEDENT
1963 I-PRECEDENT
SC I-PRECEDENT
946 I-PRECEDENT
. O

Another O
reason O
of O
the O
respondent O
as O
to O
the O
complaint O
is O
because O
his O
company O
was O
the O
corporation O
duly O
registered O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
25 I-PROVISION
of O
an O
Indian B-STATUTE
Companies I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
or O
registered O
under O
a O
Government B-ORG
of I-ORG
India I-ORG
. O

This O
matter O
also O
had O
not O
yet O
disposed O
on O
the O
presumptions O
arising O
from O
a O
Negotiable B-STATUTE
Instruments I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
. O

" O
Section B-PROVISION
158-BD I-PROVISION
in O
the O
Act O
s O
also O
provides O
greater O
flexibility O
to O
a O
police O
officer O
in O
providing O
a O
satisfaction O
report O
on O
the O
conduct O
ed O
proceedings O
in O
respect O
to O
an O
affected O
individual O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
158-BC I-PROVISION

Pw8 O
Omwati B-WITNESS
the O
daughter O
from O
Jug B-OTHER_PERSON
Lal I-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Sarti B-OTHER_PERSON
Devi I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

This O
is O
the O
case O
which O
he O
is O
able O
and O
understand O
with O
regard O
to O
his O
evidence O
held O
on O
record O
and O
held O
in O
the O
custody O
by O
the O
CBI B-ORG
. O

A O
copie O
from O
this O
notice O
shall O
be O
available O
on O
the O
address O
at O
Delhi O
CBI B-ORG
at O
Gandhinagar B-GPE
or O
its O
registered O
address O
in O
New B-GPE
Delhi I-GPE
. O

approver O
Ram B-WITNESS
Sagar I-WITNESS
Singh O
3 O
said O
on O
this O
day O
of O
the O
month O
in O
April O
that O
Raj B-OTHER_PERSON
Pal I-OTHER_PERSON
Sharma I-OTHER_PERSON
came O
into O
the O
house O
of O
Gurbachan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
to O
tell O
them O
how O
his O
wife O
Suresh B-PETITIONER
had O
come O
to O
the O
farm O
for O
his O
children O
whom O
she O
has O
called O
Gurbachan B-OTHER_PERSON
Singh I-OTHER_PERSON
. O

0 O
50 O
50 O
Colleges O
of O
MACT O
2. O
Polytechnics O

dealing O
in O
a O
sale O
for O
a O
commercial O
vehicle O
began O
and O
ended O
wholly O
or O
exclusively O
between O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
and O
London B-GPE
or O
Timbuctoo B-GPE
. O

This O
may O
explain O
how O
a O
question O
in O
respect O
to O
a O
right O
to O
the O
Palam B-GPE
be O
protected O
under O
the O
Delhi B-STATUTE
Rent I-STATUTE
Control I-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
and O
giving O
such O
a O
permit O
to O
Delhi O
government O
comes O
up O
in O
the O
Special O
Interest O
case O
filed O
in O
this O
case O
by O
the O
Palam B-ORG
Area I-ORG
Tenants I-ORG
Association I-ORG
by O
No O
4284/2000 O
known O
under O
Palam B-PRECEDENT
Area I-PRECEDENT
Tenants I-PRECEDENT
Association I-PRECEDENT
Vs. I-PRECEDENT
Union I-PRECEDENT
of I-PRECEDENT
India I-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Anr I-PRECEDENT
.. O

This O
case O
first O
appeared O
before O
my O
big O
sister O
K. B-JUDGE
Ramachandra I-JUDGE
Rap I-JUDGE
J. O

ent O
ifying O
the O
interests O
and O
needs O
? O

The O
witness O
also O
said O
the O
Meka B-OTHER_PERSON
Narasimha I-OTHER_PERSON
Rao I-OTHER_PERSON
went O
with O
Diwancheruvu B-GPE
as O
he O
did O
indeed O
know O
that O
Veerayya B-OTHER_PERSON
executed O
any O
second O
will O
subsequently O
he O
also O
attested O
to O
original O
of O
the O
second O
wish O
at O
his O
death O
of O
Veerayya B-OTHER_PERSON
. O

A O
major O
operation O
is O
conducted O
for O
his O
head O
and O
mb O
in O
Dr. O
Ram B-ORG
Manohar I-ORG
Lohia I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
. O

No O
such O
right O
has O
been O
given O
any O
Indian O
women O
by O
any O
Indian B-STATUTE
Constitution I-STATUTE
. O

Court O
relies O
for O
this O
case O
on O
Hastimal B-PRECEDENT
Dalichand I-PRECEDENT
Bora I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Hiralal I-PRECEDENT
Motichand I-PRECEDENT
Muthe I-PRECEDENT
- O
30 O
- O
Kumar O
Saha B-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Co. I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Ishar I-PRECEDENT
Singh I-PRECEDENT
Kripal I-PRECEDENT
Singh I-PRECEDENT
. O

Section B-PROVISION
113 I-PROVISION
conferred O
powers O
on O
Her O
Majesty O
for O
creating O
the O
independent O
Supreme O
Court O
for O
the O
territory O
of O
British O
India B-GPE
. O

There O
can O
no O
any O
doubt O
all O
of O
the O
named O
men O
has O
contributed O
their O
lot O
in O
the O
sport O
for O
India O
as O
all O
have O
be O
recruited O
by O
a O
regular O
channel O
according O
to O
the O
system O
for O
sports O
men O
under O
the O
1988 O
Rules O
passed O
by O
Sports O
State O
Commission O
in O
addition O
to O
its O
power O
as O
part O
of O
Article B-PROVISION
309 I-PROVISION
of O
National O
Constitution B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
India I-STATUTE
. O

The O
decision O
by O
an O
Andhra B-COURT
Pradesh I-COURT
High I-COURT
Court I-COURT
does O
not O
go O
into O
a O
conclusion O
that O
a O
declaratory O
order O
in O
that O
nature O
only O
could O
be O
passed O
by O
the O
judge O
because O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
9 I-PROVISION
in O
a O
Code B-STATUTE
of I-STATUTE
Civil I-STATUTE
Procedure I-STATUTE
. O

Each O
bottle O
is O
marked O
with O
a O
seal O
of O
CBI B-ORG
. O

This O
is O
nobody's O
case O
that O
no O
notice O
was O
given O
to O
these O
companies O
after O
entry O
in O
force O
the O
NCT B-CASE_NUMBER
E I-CASE_NUMBER
R I-CASE_NUMBER
egulations I-CASE_NUMBER
2009 I-CASE_NUMBER
. O

He O
also O
placed O
reliance O
upon O
documents O
already O
on O
file O
that O
clearly O
show O
s O
former O
home O
of O
a O
woman O
located O
at O
Calcutta B-GPE
. O

Use O
under O
Section B-PROVISION
29 I-PROVISION
in O
the O
Contract B-STATUTE
Act I-STATUTE
was O
not O
the O
only O
matter O
causing O
concern O
for O
the O
learned O
Judges O
of O
our O
Supreme B-COURT
Court I-COURT
at O
D. B-PRECEDENT
Gobindram I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Shamji I-PRECEDENT
K I-PRECEDENT
& I-PRECEDENT
Co. I-PRECEDENT
, O
. O

A O
learned O
Federal O
Sessions O
Judge O
had O
made O
an O
order O
in O
law O
or O
judgment O
in O
favor O
of O
Mr O
Shribhagwan B-PETITIONER
Sharma I-PETITIONER
in O
offence O
of O
Section B-PROVISION
307 I-PROVISION
of O
IPC B-STATUTE
. O
18. O

These O
consignments O
under O
question O
are O
sent O
from O
Junnor-Deo B-GPE
to O
Indore B-GPE
. O

The O
police O
did O
not O
followed O
all O
the O
three O
entered O
into O
Agra B-GPE
Hotel O
in O
around O
10.30 O
P. O
M. O

All O
issues O
and O
differences O
of O
both O
Plaintiffs O
and O
the O
Court O
broken O
down O
below O
is O
subject O
to O
for O
sole O
Arbitration O
by O
Justice O
Thomas O
M. B-JUDGE
L. I-JUDGE
Pendse I-JUDGE
. O

It O
will O
also O
be O
competent O
and O
make O
the O
decision O
to O
create O
monopolies O
in O
any O
State O
Government O
with O
participation O
of O
the O
commercial O
or O
industrial O
sector O
s O
if O
so O
much O
authority O
is O
already O
established O
for O
the O
Union O
under O
Article B-PROVISION
298 I-PROVISION
of O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
. O

Application O
of O
Medical B-ORG
Council I-ORG
of I-ORG
India I-ORG
and O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
on O
grant O
d O
List O
ing O
Intent O
31st B-DATE
December I-DATE
4 I-DATE
. O
Issue O
d O
List O
of O
Intent O
by O
the O
Central B-ORG
Government I-ORG
31st B-DATE
January I-DATE
5 I-DATE
. O

A O
High B-COURT
Court I-COURT
of I-COURT
Madras I-COURT
has O
therefore O
not O
yet O
to O
issue O
any O
judgment O
under O
article B-PROVISION
226 I-PROVISION
in O
the O
Constitution B-STATUTE
against O
an O
Election B-ORG
Commission I-ORG
. O

The O
report O
set O
out O
key O
criteria O
in O
respect O
to O
successful O
selection O
of O
female O
candidates O
seeking O
entry O
to O
the O
top O
academic O
programs O
in O
Kerala B-GPE
. O

This O
roster O
has O
not O
been O
sent O
nor O
was O
it O
an O
administrative O
matter O
under O
Special B-CASE_NUMBER
Appeal I-CASE_NUMBER
32 I-CASE_NUMBER
of I-CASE_NUMBER
2014 I-CASE_NUMBER
, O
as O
therefore O
it O
is O
more O
appropriate O
from O
either O
side O
of O
this O
office O
to O
having O
been O
making O
this O
order O
for O
the O
Bench O
that O
had O
no O
roster O
sent O
to O
it. O

Both O
these O
bill O
s O
should O
have O
harmonized O
bring O
to O
mind O
this O
fact O
as O
both O
contain O
ed O
the O
restatements O
on O
the O
need O
for O
equality O
enshrined O
by O
Article B-PROVISION
14 I-PROVISION
. O

Ms O
Yaseen B-OTHER_PERSON
Bi I-OTHER_PERSON
is O
the O
sister O
to O
former O
defendant-respondent O
Abdu B-RESPONDENT
Rasool I-RESPONDENT
. O

Some O
among O
those O
15 O
people O
reported O
injuries O
to O
the O
persons O
which O
appeared O
may O
have O
led O
the O
lathi O
es O
in O
village O
Khabra B-GPE
. O

For O
those O
reasons O
I O
am O
on O
a O
view O
that O
that O
the O
statement O
by O
appellant O
Arun B-PETITIONER
about O
Bhola B-OTHER_PERSON
Nath I-OTHER_PERSON
Das I-OTHER_PERSON
based O
upon O
a O
release O
in O
a O
video O
by O
Sadhana B-OTHER_PERSON
and O
Swadhinata O
is O
not O
taken O
by O
this O
learned O
Judge O
m O
consideration O
and O
was O
an O
incriminating O
circumstance O
for O
appellant O
Arun B-PETITIONER
. O

During O
seizure O
whatever O
is O
gonna O
get O
taken O
with O
the O
property O
the O
steps O
to O
be O
adopted O
from O
police O
officers O
are O
all O
laid O
out O
under O
Rules B-PROVISION
27 I-PROVISION
and I-PROVISION
28 I-PROVISION
. O

The O
first O
case O
related O
here O
was O
case O
of O
Revati B-PRECEDENT
Mohan I-PRECEDENT
Das I-PRECEDENT
v. I-PRECEDENT
Jatindra I-PRECEDENT
Mohan I-PRECEDENT
Ghose I-PRECEDENT
. O

Appellant O
Rakesh B-PETITIONER
Kumar I-PETITIONER
@ I-PETITIONER
Bhutto I-PETITIONER
Party O
President O
Parminder B-PETITIONER
Singh I-PETITIONER
Bajwa I-PETITIONER
is O
reaching O
his O
goal O
through O
financial O
help O
by O
Sir O
Ajay B-PETITIONER
Kumar I-PETITIONER
, O
Narender B-PETITIONER
Kumar I-PETITIONER
and O
Sunil B-PETITIONER
Kumar I-PETITIONER
. O

Section O
863 O
to O
865 O
contain O
paras O
10 O
and O
16 O
which O
are O
the O
follows O
: O

In O
a O
first O
circumstance O
where O
there O
was O
A1 O
Sunil B-PETITIONER
that O
took O
a O
child O
from O
taking O
advantage O
by O
PW8 O
Tara B-WITNESS
, O
police O
has O
identified O
PW8 O
Tara B-WITNESS
with O
her O
sister O
PW12 O
- O
Dariba B-WITNESS
after O
hearing O
evidence O
of O
PW10 O
Sharda B-WITNESS
. O

